Max 谢谢你愿意融入圣诞气氛
Max, thanks for agreeing to get in the spirit
做节日蛋糕
and do holiday cupcakes.
这比去年好多了 你当时喝得烂醉
So much better than last year when you go so drunk,
把圣诞十二日
you turned the 12 days of Christmas
变成圣诞十二步了
into the 12 steps of Christmas.
是啊 我终于屈服了
Yeah, well, I finally gave in.
圣诞就像疱疹一样
Christmas is like herpes.
不管你做什么
No matter what you do,
它还是每年都发作一次
it's gonna flare up once a year.
哦 你做了"圣诞快乐"纸杯蛋糕
Oh, you made Feliz Navidad cupcake.
我为你感到"灰"常骄傲
I'm muy proud of you.
而且我觉得咱们不久之后
And I think we're going to make muy mucho moolah
就能赚灰常多滴钱
when Manuel comes manana.
我认识的讲西班牙的人当中
You're the only person I know
就你一个人比较白一点
who seems whiter speaking Spanish.
"圣诞快乐" 送给说西班牙语的朋友们
Feliz Navidad for our Spanish speaking friends.
而这个刚是献给像我这样的孩子 "他不是你爹"快乐
And for kids raised like me,  Feliz "He's-not-your-dad."
接下来 "欢乐世界" 送给普通人
And then, "Joy To The World" for the normals,
送给嬉皮士的呢 就是"大麻世界"
and for the hipsters, "Joint To The World."
送给小孩的 "霜白的雪人"
For the kids, "Frosty The Snowman."
还有送给你的 "冻死没男人"
And for you, "Frosty With No Man."
好吧 杰克冻人也没有去捏揉你的乳头啊
Well, I didn't see Jack Frost nipping at your nips either.
哦 看这里 这个是我的最爱
Oh, here, this one's my favorite,
"圣诞老人来..."
"Santa Claus Is Coming"...
Max 别说了
Max, stop right there.
不 我没别的意思 他来了
No, that was it. He's coming.
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组  http://hdscg.com/ ==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 影子
翻译: Astral Morning 浅陷夜蓝 波特妹子
校对: 桃茜茜
Earl 找钱
Earl, change please.
"Earl 找钱"
"Earl, change please."
我两个前妻都对我说过这话
A phrase I heard from both my ex-wives.
哇 你的圣诞贺卡
Wow, you have more Christmas cards
比奥斯卡.皮斯托瑞斯的借口都多
than Oscar Pistorius had excuses.
我能说什么呢 Max? 我处处施善
What can I say, Max? I spread a lot of goodwill.
我所有的裇衫也是因此得来的
It's also where I get all of my shirts.
拿着 节日快乐
Here you go. Have a nice holiday.
我的两个孩子们最爱每年的这个时候了
My two kids love this time of year.
到明年圣诞 我就会有三个孩子了
And next Christmas, there will be three.
是个男孩
It's a boy.
我在阿富汗的老公接到这电话非常高兴
My husband was so happy when I called him in Afghanistan.
每年这时候讨小费都好容易
Man, this time of year people are easier
比胖妞穿抹胸还要容易
than a fat girl in a tube top.
太好了 咱们可以用这个钱
Oh, great. We can use this money
多订做一些纸杯蛋糕T恤衫
to order more of our cupcake T-shirts.
不行 我们要用这个钱给大家买圣诞礼物
No, we are using that to buy people Christmas gifts.
我真的很希望自己在送礼物给别人之后
I was really looking forward to giving someone something
不必再去打几针治性病
that wouldn't require the follow-up penicillin shot.
我们需要更多的T恤衫 这些东西卖得可好了
We need more shirts. These are really selling.
四号桌的那个家伙说 这礼物
The guy at table four said it's the perfect gift
送给只谈性不谈爱的炮友最合适了
for a girl you're not in love with, just strictly banging.
他买了三件
He bought three.
我碰巧知道
I happen to know for a fact
这里的所有人都我们买了礼物
that everyone here's getting us stuff.
Han今天进来的时候拿着一个小包
Han came in with a small package today
还有一个礼物袋
and also he was carrying a gift bag.
我们会搞到买礼物的钱
We'll find some money for the gifts.
大家也没指望着能有啥大的
People aren't expecting anything big.
节日快乐
Happy holidays.
别人想要大的东西 有些人都没有
People just got the nothing big they were expecting.
集合一下好吗 我有一份很特殊的礼物
Gather, please. I have a very special gift
要送给我的餐馆员工们
for all my diner employees.
健康保险?
Health insurance?
拜托 这是圣诞节 不是疯子节
Come on, it's Christmastime, not crazy time.
这是个艺术品 有着独一无二的丝绢网印花
It's art. It's a one of a kind silk screen.
这是我亲手做的
I did it by hand.
我想你一直都是自己用手的啊
I figured that's how you always have to do it.
Han 这是我们的餐馆 太棒了
Han, it's the diner. This is amazing.
把门打开 我在门后还印有东西哦
Open the door. I put something behind it
这是我对你们的印象
that reminds me of each of you.
我的贺卡上有Sophie
Mine has Sophie.
我的贺卡上有个萨克斯
Mine has a saxophone.
我的上面有个纸杯蛋糕
Mine has a cupcake.
我的上面有个电锯
Mine has a chainsaw.
嘿 大家好!
Hey, everybody!
圣诞购物小贴士
Holiday shopping tip:
在星巴克的咖啡杯里装满伏特加
Fill a Starbucks cup with vodka.
这对女服务员也有用
Also good for waitressing.
Sophie 你去圣诞购物了?
Sophie, were you Christmas shopping?
哦 你懂得的!
Oh, you know I was!
接线板!
Power strips!
哦 太好了 你买了冲击电压保护器
Oh good. You got surge protectors.
哇 那可是你第一次在自己家中
Wow, that's the first time protection's
采取保护措施
ever been used in your apartment.
我的圣诞装扮需要7万5瓦特的电压
Well, my Christmas village needs 75,000 watts.
这还只够给我的糖果直升机用
And that's just to work my candy cane helicopter.
Sophie最近一直在忙着参加波兰联合社装扮大赛
Sophie's been so busy with the Polish Society Decorating Contest.
我们已经好几天没有做爱了
We haven't had sex in days.
好吧 我得打败我的死对头 Felka Bobenski
Well, I got to beat my nemesis, Felka Bobenski.
她每年都拿第一
She wins every year.
她就像圣诞装扮界里的"摩登家庭"
She's like the Modern Family of Christmas decorations
你知道今年谁要过忧伤圣诞节了吗?
You know who's having a blue Christmas this year?
我的蛋蛋
My balls.
我爱圣诞节中的这座城市
I love this city at the holidays.
是啊 尿都冻住了
Yeah, the urine's all frozen
你根本闻不到味道
so you can't really smell it.
曼哈顿是买高档的圣诞礼物最好的地方了
Manhattan is the best place to buy quality Christmas gifts.
我们有40块钱
We have 40 bucks.
那些装满了
Now, where are those duffel bags
由东非难民偷来半价出售的
full of stolen electronics sold for half the price
电子元件的大袋子在哪?
by Nairobi refugees?
我们得赶紧找到
Well, we better find them soon
不然我就得像别人那样
or I'm going to give up and go to Radio Shack
去逛电子市场了
like everyone else who goes to Radio Shack.
天啊 Max
Oh my God, Max.
我的童年银行
My childhood bank.
你有一个童年银行?
You had a childhood bank?
我连童年都没有
I didn't even have a childhood.
来吧 我们走 我每隔几个月都会进去
Come on, let's go. I stop in every few months
让监控拍我几张照片
to get caught on the security cameras,
好让别人以为我还在那个圈子里
so people will think I'm still in the mix.
你想被监控拍到自己?
Trying to get caught on security cameras?
哇 我们真是太不同了
Whoa, we are different.
我们进去吧 在里面的时候
Yeah, we'll just go in and while we're in here,
要不咱们去搞个商业贷款吧
well, I don't know, ask for a business loan.
我们才不要去商业贷款!
We are not getting a business loan!
你要想骗我进城
You tricked me into coming to the city.
至少也得把我敲晕 然后像人一样塞进后车箱吧
At least knock me out and put me in the trunk like a person.
好 我听你的 不贷款
Okay, I hear you. No loan.
但是我们能否至少进去走一下
But can we at least go in there
让我闻一下金库的味道
so I can get a hit off some vault fumes
再来杯免费的圣诞可可?
and a complimentary Christmas cocoa?
好 我也要一杯
Yeah, I want one too.
这外面太冷了
It's so cold out here
我的胸罩都要起诉我的胸骚扰它了
my bra is suing my nipples for assault.
不如咱们贷个15000美元吧
I'd say we ask for $15,000.
这里近得我几乎闻到一百块的味道了
So close I almost smelled a 100.
你是怎么了?
What is with you?
要是我想让你一直骗我
If I wanted you to keep lying to me,
我就会跟你约会了
I'd date you.
Max 我们需要更多资金
Max, we need more capital
这样就能大量购买我们的T恤
so we can buy our shirts in bulk,
然后 如果我们再努力点工作
and then, if we work even harder,
我们就能获得双倍利润
we can double our profit.
我们甚至连信用检查都通过不了的
Okay, we won't pass even the credit check.
根据我的社保号
According to my Social Security number,
我在几年前的船爆炸中死了
I died in a boat explosion years ago.
现在申请的好时候
This is the time to apply.
银行家在圣诞节时更容易心软
Bankers have more guilt at Christmastime
因为"生活多美好"
because of It's A Wonderful Life.
圣诞节经典电影 准备自杀的主人公遇到天使并重振旗鼓的故事
而且他们是犹太人 不过圣诞节
And also 'cause they're Jewish.
我可是拿了商学院学位的
I'm the one with the business degree,
这一点你一定要相信我
and you have to trust me on this.
你知道吗? 你说得对
You know what? You're right.
你是商业天才 而我知道什么?
You're the business genius. What do I know?
我们去借贷款
Let's go get that loan.
谢谢!
Thank you!
好吧 我就该知道你哪有这么好说话
Yeah, I should have known that was too good to be true.
Max 别这样
Max, come on.
银行就在那儿 我们的T恤就在这里
The bank's there. Our shirt's in here.
我们只要进去 给他们看 然后申请贷款
Let's just go in, show them, and apply for that loan.
- 求你了!  - 不
- Please!  - No.
就在那儿有个小东西
And that right there was a little something
写着"我们要银行贷款"
called "us asking for a bank loan."
现在走吧
Now let's go.
我不会走的 除非你告诉我
I'm not leaving here until you tell me
你究竟在担心什么
what the underlying issue is.
我再也不爱你了
I'm not in love with you anymore.
Max 认真点
Max, be serious.
这整件T裇都是你的创意
This whole T-shirt was your idea.
真正的问题是什么?
What's the real problem?
这就是问题所在
That's the problem.
这些T恤是我的主意
Those shirts were my idea
我想出来的东西从不值一万五
and nothing that comes from me is worth $15,000.
除了我在如意宝贝店卖出的那个婴儿
Aside from that baby I sold on E-baby.
Max 我知道这些T恤是赚钱的玩意儿
Max, I know these T-shirts are a money-maker.
哦 我有赚钱的玩意儿 但不是它
Oh, I have a money-maker and that's not it.
我可以证明
I can prove it.
看 这是Rodney
Look, this is Rodney,
我童年的高档服装店
my childhood over-priced clothing store.
早知道我们今天是去游览童年
If I had known we were going on the childhood tour today,
我就会穿一双更舒服的鞋子
I would have worn more comfortable shoes
并且呆在家里
and stayed home.
看见模特身上那件T恤吗?
See the shirt on the mannequin?
至少两百美元
At least $200.
我们的T恤没理由卖不到相同的价钱
And there's no reason we can't sell ours for just as much.
我会证明给你看 跟着我
I'll show you. Follow me.
好 我会关注你的 但不是在照片网上
Oh, okay, I will. But not on Instagram,
因为你已经是晒照狂人
'cause you're out of control.
这地方真花哨
This place is fancy
连纽瓦克的新港务局都会自叹不如
and I've been to the new Port Authority in Newark.
相信我 好吗?
Just trust me, okay?
你要穿着Wang(品牌)的高跟鞋跳两下
You need to jump on those Wang pumps
或者像本·阿弗莱克演的那样 成为"消失的爱人"
or like Ben Affleck, they will be "Gone, girl."
本·阿弗莱克出演了电影"消失的爱人"
让我来说 我会说他的语言
Let me do the talking. I speak his language.
那是什么语言? 葡萄基佬语?
And what language is that? Portu-gays?
你好 女士们 欢迎光临Rodney
Hello, ladies. Welcome to Rodney.
我是Barry
I'm Barry.
你们是在假日购物吗?
Doing a little holiday shopping?
我们不能说圣诞节
We're not allowed to say Christmas.
实际上 我们是在假日出售
As a matter of fact, we're doing a little holiday selling.
哦 你在"出售"
Oh, you're "selling."
懂了 摇头丸? 可卡因?
Got it. Molly? Coke?
我都不感兴趣
Not that I'm interested.
自从火岛2010年的缉毒行动后我就戒了
I've been clean since Fire Island 2010.
还有2012年那时
And 2012.
不嗑嗨却要做自己 这很难受吧
It must be hard to not be high and be you.
因为不能嗑嗨了却要靠近你
Because it's hard for me
这让我觉得很难受
to just be near you and not be high.
你懂的 妹子
Yeah, you get it, girl.
实际上我们是想看看你是否有兴趣
Actually, we wanted to see if you'd be interested
卖我们这种图案超棒的T恤
in selling one of our fabulous graphic t-shirts.
哦 不不不不不...
Oh, n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n-n...
各种"不" 好吗?
all sorts of "no", okay?
虽然爱土耳其毡帽 配腰带的长袍 以及男孩子
As much as I love a fez, a caftan, and a teenage boy,
但这里不是摩洛哥
this isn't Morocco.
真是一长串烦人的"不"
That's a really long and boring version of "No."
就像你说"不! 独角戏(品牌)时装秀"
It's like you just did  "No! The One Woman Show."
这是我们的T恤...
Here's our T-shirt...
看看
Look.
知道我是怎么对年轻的马克·雅可布说的吗
I'll tell you two what I said to a young Marc Jacobs.
别送给我 我不要垃圾货
Stop offering, I'm off the junk.
节日快乐
Merry Holiday.
我要让圣母知道啥叫节日
I'll show Mary a holiday.
咱们的裇衫和这些一样好
Our shirts are just as good as these.
他只要看了就知道
He just needs to see it.
给你 拿着
Here, hold this.
你是谁? 美国精神病人?
What are you? American Psycho?
一旦有人对你说"不"
As soon as someone says "No" to you,
你就开始肢解女人
you start dismembering women.
我脱不下她的T恤
I can't get her shirt off.
告诉她 她可以过夜
Tell her she can spend the night
而你早上会给她买华夫饼
and you'll buy her a waffle in the morning.
好了 把咱们的T恤给我
Okay, hand me our shirt.
我觉得这将是我们关键的一步
I think this is gonna be big for us.
你还觉得Michael Buble(爵士歌手)唱摇滚呢
You also think Michael Buble rocks.
哦 我要抓紧了 Barry快出来了
Oh, I have to hurry. Barry is coming.
Barry快出来了
Barry is coming.
看来你是爱和陌生人爱爱啊
I'm guessing mostly with strangers.
真的假的?
Seriously?
不!是!吧?
Ser-I-ous-ly?
好可爱
So cute.
看看后面 写着"奶油爆满"
And look on the back, "Cream Filled."
有趣
Funny.
人们会觉得我很有个性
People will think I have a personality.
Barry 把这件和我要其他那些都放一起
Barry, put this with my other stuff.
多少钱?
How much?
三百块
300.
还说什么戒掉了 那家伙嗨了吧
Forget the sober story. That guy is high.
给我来十件
I'll take ten.
对于我那些不讨厌自己胳膊的朋友来说
They'll make great Hanukkah gifts
这会是很棒的光明节礼物
for my friends who don't hate their arms.
我们的T恤刚被一个有钱的死女人买了
All our shirts just got bought by a rich dead lady.
周五前再给我来三十件
I'll need 30 more by Friday.
是的 我还在等
Yes, I'm still holding.
我要下一个紧急的T恤订单
I need to place a rush t-shirt order.
不行 不行 不能让我再等了
No, no, no, no, no. Don't put me on hold again.
我已经听了七遍
I've been through seven rounds of
"奶奶被驯鹿撞倒了"这歌
Grandma Got Run Over By A Reindeer.
她又被撞了一遍
And she just got run over again.
咱们现在从疯基佬那里赚了点钱
Now that we have all this crazy gay t-shirt money,
我想我们应该再买贵点的礼物
I think we should up the prices on these gifts.
所以咱们一致决定给Earl送一辆车
So we agree, we're getting Earl a car.
送Sophie一幢她梦寐以求的湖边乡间别墅
Sophie is getting the country house with the lake she's always wanted.
Max Rodney把咱的T恤卖三百一件
Max, Rodney is selling our shirts for 300,
但咱们只能赚25块
but we only get 25 of that.
750块钱可买不了一幢房子
And you can't buy a house for $750.
因为咱们不在底特律
It's not Detroit.
是的 嗨 终于来了个人接电话
Yes, hi, hi, hi. Finally a person.
周五前我要五十件T恤
I need 50 T-shirts by Friday.
但是你们名片写着 你们确保翌日邮递
But your business card says you guarantee next-day delivery.
哦 你不能"确保"那个保证?
Oh, you can't "Guarantee" that guarantee?
好了 说到Oleg
Okay, now Oleg.
这个一无所有 但是让你
What do you get a man who has nothing,
一览无遗的男人 你还能送他什么
but shows you everything?
什么叫"还有什么需要帮忙的吗?"
What do you mean "Is there anything else you can help me with?"
你究竟有帮到我什么
When did you help me at all?
我现在开始想 如果奶奶真的为你们工作
And I'm beginning to think if Grandma works for you,
她不是被驯鹿撞死的
she didn't get run over by that reindeer,
她是自己一头撞死在雪橇车的
she threw herself under a sleigh.
送给Sophie一瓶斯纳普饮料
So, Sophie's getting a Snapple.
跟去年一样
Like last year.
Max 我们不能放弃 我们可以自己完成
Max, we can't give up. We can do them ourselves.
我们只需要找人完成
We just need someone else to do them.
来吧 快出去
Come on, let's go.
外面有顾客等好久了
There are customers who have been here
罗宾·西克也等了好久才红
since Robin Thicke was relevant.
等等 Han 你丝印了那些漂亮的卡片
Wait a minute, Han. You silk-screened all those beautiful cards.
你在艺术方面有才能
You have an artistic side.
是的 只是后面没曲线
Yeah, but no backside.
而且他的正面影响市容
And a front side that shouldn't be allowed outside.
你为什么这么慢啊?
Why is this taking so long?
连那些圣诞卡你你丝印了
You did all those Christmas cards.
难道不是个子越小的动作就越快吗?
Aren't small creatures supposed to be fast?
说实话 那些卡片是去年就应该做好的
Truth be told, those were supposed to be ready last year.
但是 着什么急呢?
But, what was the rush?
反正你俩也没事干
You two weren't going anywhere.
Han 你只要说"是"或"不是"就行
Han, just a simple "Yes" or "No".
我们不做评论
No judgment.
你有没有跟这台机器做爱?
Have you had sex with this machine?
比你们俩给我打工更糟糕的事
The only thing worse than you two working for me
就是我给你们打工
is me working for you.
连口水都不给我喝
You haven't even given me water.
水是给工人喝的
Water is for closers.
我说的"工人"是指真正制作衣服的人
By "closers," I mean people who actually make clothes.
谁啊?
Who's that?
Han 你是不是向儿童保护机构举报我们了?
Han, did you call Child Protective Service on us?
那些淤青可能是任何人造成的
'Cause those bruises could be from anyone.
Han 两个小时你才弄好一件
Han, you've only made one shirt in two hours.
这可是杰作 你想要一个公民凯恩那样的经典
And it's a masterpiece. Do you want one Citizen Kane
还是三十个好景在望那样的烂片?
or 30 Here Comes the Booms?
同志们 我需要你们的帮助
Guys, I need your help.
Sophie就在我后面 需要让她高兴起来
Sophie's right behind me and needs some cheering up.
自从她昨晚在嘿咻的中途中醒来
I haven't seen her this depressed
我从未见过她这么沮丧的
since she woke up mid-coitus last night.
嗨
Hi.
嗨 嗨 丫头们
Hi. Hi, girls.
圣诞节快乐
Merry Christmas.
问个问题
Quick question:
如果我打开灶 关上窗户
if I were to turn on that oven and close all the windows,
我会死吗?
would I die?
不会
Nope.
否则我也会不站在
Otherwise I wouldn't be standing here
效率低下的金正"一"旁边
next to Kim Jong-Only-Done-One.
Sophie 怎么回事?
Sophie, what's the problem?
告诉Han 让他赶紧干活
Tell Han while he gets back to work.
Han 你快点
And Han, pick up the pace
否则我又要掐你了
or I'm going to start the pinching again.
我要输掉圣诞节装饰比赛了
I'm gonna lose the Christmas decorating contest.
我没有活下去的念头了
Oh, I have nothing to live for.
Caroline 也许你每天都是这种感觉
Oh, Caroline, this is probably how you feel every day.
Sophie的对手在她门前
Sophie's competition made a live-action
搞了场北极实时表演
North Pole workshop in front of her house.
我楼上只有灯火通明的耶稣出生地
Well, all I got upstairs is a light-up nativity
和价值两万五的圣诞节装饰品
and $25,000 worth of Target Christmas decorations.
她昨晚烧坏了五根保险丝
She blew five fuses last night.
我从未想过我会嫉妒保险丝
I never thought I'd be jealous of a fuse.
Sophie 我们真的没时间弄这个
Sophie, we really can't get into this now.
我们还得把T恤赶工制好
We are way behind with these T-shirts.
这些T恤可是我们千载难逢的好机会
And these T-shirts are a once in a lifetime chance
能为我们的生意打开一片新天地
for us to go to a new place with our business.
嗯 我听到你说的了 丫头们
Oh yeah, I hear you, girls.
我到底在这里干嘛啊
I mean, what am I doing here
担心什么破比赛?
sitting worrying about some silly contest?
这可是圣诞节
It's Christmas.
来吧 同志们
Come on everybody.
我们都应该帮帮丫头们
We should all be helping the girls.
真的? 那真是太棒了
Really? That would be so amazing.
当然! 你们都不用给我工钱
Sure! And you wouldn't even have to pay me back
只要明天晚上把你们的谷仓和马借我用用
by letting me use your barn and your horse tomorrow night
我们要上演耶稣诞生 你们都要参加
for a live nativity scene, which you would all have to be in.
差不多就是这样
Or something like that.
我想咱们刚遭遇了季节性的敲诈
I think we just had a seasonal shake-down.
Han在弄最后一个 我们会完成的
Han's doing the last one. We're gonna make it.
真不敢相信 你贴着那假胡子还能这么开心
I can't believe you're in such a good mood with that beard.
上周你发现自己下巴长了两根毛时
Last week when you found those two chin hairs,
可没这么开心
you weren't so chipper.
我只是很开心有新衣服穿了
I'm just so happy I have new clothes.
好了 最后一件衬衫
Okay, final shirt.
然后你们俩就可以消失了
Then I get you two out of my angel hair.
Han 要不是你的话
Han, you know, if it weren't for you,
我们绝对完不成任务
we would have never gotten this done.
你真的是个小天使
You really are a little angel.
没错 但我还是很惊讶
Yeah, you are. But I'm still surprised
你竟然不扮婴儿
you weren't cast as the baby.
哦  我被问到来着 但我拒绝了
Oh, I was asked, but I declined.
我花了十年才摆脱尿布
I spent ten year getting out of diapers.
我才不要重新穿上
I'm not getting back in.
Han 作为你的圣诞礼物
Han, for your Christmas gift,
我就假装没听到吧
I'll pretend I never heard that.
各就各位
Places everybody.
评委们要来了 我好了
The judges are coming. I'm ready.
约瑟好了 "耶"菜娃娃好了
Joseph's ready. Cabbage Patch Christ is ready.
快
Come on!
那乳沟是怎么回事?
What's with the cleavage?
可不是
I know.
她像是非圣女玛丽亚
She's like the Not-So-Virgin Mary.
小天使 牧羊人 长胡子的小姐
Angel, Shepherd, Lady with the beard,
快点 到马厩来
come on, get in the stable.
马厩?
Stable?
我们的样子看起来更像"没救"才对
The way we look it should be an "Unstable."
都准备好了吗? 我要开谷仓门了
Everybody ready? I'm going to open the barn door.
我看你的门早就有点开了
Yeah, I think your barn door's already a little open.
那个 我是谁来着?
Okay now, who am I again?
战神?
Voltron?
我不说假话 可能有智者
I'm not gonna lie. One of the wise men
吸过"圣大麻"
might have smoked some "Myrrh-ijuana."
这份圣诞礼物很有心 Max
That was a very nice Christmas gift, Max.
谢谢 Earl 对了 Sophie
Thanks, Earl. By the way, Sophie,
谷仓加上我们穿得跟白痴似的?
the barn and us dressed like idiots?
是给你的圣诞礼物
That's your Christmas gift.
还有 一会儿跟Oleg来一炮
Oh, and hey, bang Oleg later.
Oleg 这是你的礼物
Oleg, that's your gift.
你怎么知道?
How did you know?
他们进来之前 让我们抽点时间回顾一年
Before they come in, let's just take a moment to look around
衷心迎接真正的圣诞精神吧
and really let in the true spirit of Christmas.
我不记得有给你写独白
I don't remember writing you a monologue.
给我闭嘴!
Shut up!
站到马旁边去
Get your ass over by the horse.
来吧 Han 放音乐
Come on, Han. Hit the music.
好了 各位
All right, everybody,
庄严起来
look holy.
我已经穿上内裤了
Best I can do is my underwear.
我去!
Oh , crap!
没错 Felka
Oh, that's right, Felka.
我是上帝他妈
I'm the freakin' mother of God.
我们赢了!
We won!
我好开心赢了
I'm so happy we won.
我们赢了! 我们赢了!
We won! We Won!
好了 表演结束
Okay, show's over.
扔掉孩子 我在楼上等你
Dump the kid, I'll be upstairs.
Max 照顾好"耶"菜娃娃
Max, take care of Cabbage Patch Christ.
给你 Han 你有个和你个子相仿的同伴了
Here, Han. You got a buddy your own size.
太感谢你了 Barry
Thank you so much, Barry.
别忘了 新年过后我从戒毒所回来
And remember, I want 50 more shirts
还要五十件衬衫
after the first of the year when I'm back from rehab.
因为女士们 我今年打算过一个白粉圣诞节
'Cause ladies, I am planning a very white Christmas.
Max 这真是太棒了!
Max, this is amazing!
你知道刚刚发生了什么吗?
Do you know what just happened in there?
当然 我偷了一副酷毙了的无指手套
Yeah, I stole some dope-ass fingerless gloves.
我们现在跟他们做生意呢
We're in business with them now.
你得还回去
You have to bring those back.
我为你拿的
I got them for you.
那好吧
Okay.
这就像圣诞奇迹啊
This is like a Christmas miracle.
我们的衬衫在
Our shirts are being sold in
曼哈顿最顶级的傲娇精品店出售
the most exclusive bitchy boutique in Manhattan
而且他们还要货 要很多
and they want more, lots more.
嘿 我们去你的童年银行吧
Hey, let's go into your childhood bank.
我得撒泡成人尿
I need to take an adult pee.
好吧 但这不是在家里 所以记住
Okay, but this isn't home, so remember,
完事了把马桶座放下
put the seat down when you're done.
我们在里面的时候 还可以申请贷款
And while we're in there, we can apply for that loan.
不 不 不 不行
No, no, no, no, no. We can't.
现在我害怕了
Now I'm afraid.
拜托 到底怎么回事?
Come on, what's the real issue here?
我们刚取得了惊人的成功
We just had this amazing success.
看起来事情一顺百顺
And it looks like things are going our way,
如果我们进去了 可能就都毁了
and if we go in there, it could all be ruined.
你知道怎样会更毁人生吗?
You know what would ruin our lives even more?
就是我们不申请贷款 就得长时间跟Han在一起
If we don't get that loan and have to spend hours
让他在我们"下面"做衬衫
with Han standing under us trying to finish those shirts.
好吧 那真的是"圣诞夜惊魂"了
Well, that's a real "Nightmare Before Christmas."
我们走
Let's go.
很好 因为我已经要尿出来了
Good, cause I'm starting to pee a little.
我们拿到贷款了!
He gave us a loan!
在这条街上工作的人都吸晕了吗?
Is everyone who works on the street high?
简直不敢相信 事情没有搞砸
I can't believe it. It didn't go bad.
我要的全有了
I'm getting everything I want.
你走人行道外面
Walk on the outside of the sidewalk.
我幸运得要被车撞上了
I'm gonna get hit by a bus.
他怎么能给我们贷款呢?
I mean, how could he give us a loan?
我甚至不用亮出胸器
I didn't even have to flash my boobs.
那你干嘛还给人看?
Then why did you do it?
不知道 他们这么慷慨
I don't know. They were making it rain.
我觉得有义务秀一下
I felt obliged.
Max 你有一块钱吗?
Max, do you have a dollar?
不知道 你能找开一万块吗?
I don't know. Do you have change for 10,000?
有 给你 干嘛啊?
Yeah, here. For what?
给那些不这么幸运的人
For those less fortunate.
安妮 海瑟薇来了?
Anne Hathaway's here?
天啊 快看! 快看!
Oh, my God. Look! Look!
哇 不是吧! 不会吧!
Whoa, no way! No way!
Max 我都起鸡皮疙瘩了
Max, I have chills.
因为天在下雪 手套还没有指头
Well, it is snowing and there's no fingers on those gloves.
我爱这双手套
I love these.
抱歉没有给你礼物
I'm sorry I didn't get you anything.
因为我不偷东西
I'm just not a thief.
你怎么会什么都没有给我呢?
What do you mean you didn't get me anything?
你给了我一切 看啊
You got me everything. Look.